Long story short, she's on the no-fly list...
(Bernadette:)...and we might have been
followed here by a drone.
- I'm sorry. I feel like such an idiot.
- Oh, it's not so bad. You lost money...
...you're filled with shame, you got groped
by a stranger. That's Vegas, you nailed it.
(Amy:)You guys enjoy your evening. I'm gonna go
before I ruin anybody else's weekend.
(Sheldon:)That's my girl.
(Leonard:)Amy, wait. I know it's not the night
you had in mind...
...but why don't you stay and play?
It'll be fun.
(Sheldon:)Fun?
(Sheldon:)Three weeks ago you bought
crunchy peanut butter...
(Sheldon:)...now you want the girls to play D&D
with... Do you have a drug problem?
(Leonard:)What's the big deal? Raj bailed,
so we could use some extra players.
(Sheldon:)I've just never played
Dungeons & Dragons with girls before.
(Penny:)Oh, don't worry, sweetie. No one has.
(Leonard:)So, what do you say?
(Sheldon:)I'll leave it up to the Dungeon Master.